我去问问你们的沙拉好了没
I'll go check on your salads.
Oleg 沙拉怎么还没好?
Oleg, what's the hold up with the salads?
我以前从没做过
I never made one before.
我最爱的两个人 大Doug和Sancho
My two favorite guys, Big Doug and Sancho,
他们点的是沙拉?
are ordering salads?
他们平时点的BLT呢?
What happened to their usual BLTs?
汉堡 千层面 玉米饼?
Burgers, lasagna, and tacos?
他们说想要减肥
They said they want to lose weight.
不管点什么
And no matter what you order,
比起在家吃 在这里更容易吐出来
it's easier to throw up here than at home.
我不懂 为什么大家都想要减肥
I don't get why nobody wants to be fat anymore.
奥普拉胖的时候 节目一直是最棒的
The fat seasons of Oprah were always the best.
说得对
You're right.
奥普拉不胖的时候也只有一年吧
Every other year of Oprah was the best years.
我听说你们两位害羞小可爱要节食?
What is this I hear about you blushing beauties on a diet?
哦 我们不是害羞得脸红
Oh, we're not blushing.
只是坐下运动过后的脸红
We're just still flushed from sitting down.
我们想保持身材
And we're trying to get in shape.
对 身材最好不要像
Yeah, preferably a shape that doesn't resemble
一个季节性的葫芦
a seasonal gourd.
而且 我女朋友想让我瘦下来
Plus my girlfriend wants me to slim down
这样我们出行时 就能坐在飞机的同一侧
so we can sit on the same side of the plane when we travel.
大Doug
Well, Big Doug,
你告诉那个幸运的女士 我更愿意
you tell that lucky lady that I would rather date a man
和胸部大过我的男人约会
with boobs bigger than mine
而不愿跟一个自带沙拉酱去餐厅的人约会
than a man who brings his own salad dressing to a restaurant.
给我个派
Pie me.
樱桃 南瓜 还是椰奶馅儿?
Cherry, pumpkin, or coconut cream?
全要
Yes.
我 Max Black
Max Black,
自发育以来 一直为男人脸上带来微笑
bringing smiles to men's faces since puberty.
破产姐妹花 第四季第21集
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组  http://hdscg.com/ ==--
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调: 。沫   校对: 酱油影
翻译: Morning 落寞卷菜 jujo
我刚刚聊天的那个人坐在...
I just talked to this guy at...
应该是三号桌 我还是记不住桌号
I think it's table three, I still don't know the numbers.
不管怎样 他问了句"有什么新推荐?"
Anyway, he asked, "What's new?"
我告诉他 我们明天将在机场
And I told him we were opening a dessert bar
开一间甜品店
at the airport tomorrow.
后来我意识到 他问的是
Then I realized he was asking what kind of pot
这周我卖哪种大麻
I was selling this week.
你为什么要跟别人聊我们和机场的事?
Why are you telling people about us and the airport?
这就像是告诉别人你觉得自己得了人乳突瘤病毒
It's like when you told everyone you thought you had HPV.
那算是政府委托的
That was a state-mandated kind of thing.
哦 看这是谁啊...
Oh, look who it is...
机场工作人员
the airport people.
你们俩一起度过欢乐时光?
You guys putting together a little happy hour?
和西南部的肌肉男一起?
With the jocks at Southwest?
还是和处女终点站的"小圈子"一起?
Or the "in crowd" at the Virgin Terminal?
你知道谁会是最后的处子吗?
You know who's going to be a terminal virgin?
你们可以随意做尽各种死亡威胁
You can make all the death threats you want,
但你们知道什么会让我活下来吗?
but you know what will keep me alive?
就是你们在机场工作的事实
The fact that you two work at the airport.
嘿 姑娘们!
Hey, everybody!
准新娘来了
Here comes the almost bride.
你们见过更漂亮的准新娘吗?
Did you ever see a prettier almost bride?
当然了 除开詹妮弗・安妮斯顿
I mean, you know, besides Jennifer Aniston.
Sophie 只剩一周就到婚礼了
Sophie, it's only one week till the wedding,
所以这是你投向我怀抱的最后机会
so this is your last chance to take a run at me.
你不会失望的
Now you won't be disappointed.
我在前五分钟
I'm still very sexually active
还是很性致勃勃的
for the first five minutes.
哦 Earl
Oh, Earl.
要是我投向你
If I took a run at you,
你会像骗子郊狼一样 直接穿过那面墙的
you'd go right through that wall like Wile E. Coyote.
骗子郊狼: 出自卡通片"公路奔驰鸟/Road Runner"
嘿 伴娘
Hey, bridesmaid.
嘿 Sophie
Hey, Sophie.
嘿 Oleg
Hey, Oleg.
你乌克兰的哥哥给你留了言
You got a message from your brother in the Ukraine.
Yoshinko来电话了?
Yoshinko called?
对 你听这条留言
Yeah, hear this message.
什么留言?
What was the message?
"嘿 Oleg 你看见昨晚的外星生物了吗?"
"Hey, Oleg, did you see last night's Alf?"
不... 我不会说乌克兰语
Nah... I don't speak Ukrainian.
我又不是皇后区的妓女
I mean, what am I, a plumber in Queens?
不是 所以我把整部机器带来了
No, so I brought the whole thing in.
开始
Here he is.
嘿 Oleg...
Oleg...
再见
Good-bye.
他说了什么?
What did he say?
他不会来
He's not coming.
我听懂了一点
I understood a little
因为我有个一起长大的俄国交换生朋友
'cause I had a Russian Au pair growing up.
在她把我好好的牛仔裤漂白之前
You know, until she bleached my good jeans.
Yoshinko不能来参加婚礼
Yoshinko can't come to the wedding.
他上了禁飞名单 禁驾名单
He's on a no-fly list, a no-drive list,
还有禁走名单
and a no-walk list.
他进监狱了
He's in jail.
哦 但他本来要给你当伴郎的啊
Oh, but he was gonna be your best man.
我都给他留好火腿了
I got a ham engraved for him.
别担心 宝贝 我会找别人的
Don't worry, baby, I'll find someone.
谁都可以
It could be anyone.
他不一定是最好的 甚至不好都行
He doesn't even have to be the best or even good.
我会降低我的标准
I'll have to lower my standards.
嘿 Han
Han,
你可以当我的伴郎吗?
will you be my best man?
你说的是降低 不是低到地下两层
You said lower, not sub-basement.
Oleg 我得考虑考虑
Well, Oleg, I'll need to think about it.
可以
Yes.
很好 那么Han
Great. So Han,
你负责明天的告别单身派对
you're in charge of the bachelor party tomorrow.
我想一个颜面尽失的夜晚
I want a night that will disgrace all involved.
一个人会让所有人都不敢在第二天的早午餐上
A night where no one can look each other in the eye
直视对方的夜晚
at brunch the next day.
哇 Han
Wow, Han.
告别单身派对的担子可不小
Bachelor party's a big responsibility.
你认识能替你买啤酒的大人吗?
Do you know any grown-ups who can buy you beer?
Max 快点
Max, hurry.
这个粉红的机场地牢几分钟后
The grand opening of this pink airport dungeon
就要隆重开张了
is in a few minutes.
运输安全局那一关过了好久
That TSA line took forever.
那个一身镍币的女人?
The woman with all those nickels?
自查兹・波诺以来 我没见过一个女人身上有这么大变化(这么多零钱)
I haven't seen that much change on a lady since Chaz Bono.
查兹・波诺: 女变男的易性人
别担心
Don't worry,
我正在跟运输安全局的人交朋友
I'm making friends in the TSA.
Judy 一个大姑娘 有点山羊胡?
Judy, big gal, little beard?
在马航旁边的中餐馆
Having lunch with her at the Wok N' Roll
跟她一起吃午饭
near Malaysia Airlines.
这些天 那里特别安静
It's pretty quiet over there these days.
嘿 女士们
Hey, ladies.
开业日 我太激动了
Opening day, I'm so excited
从我醒来开始 我的乳头就一直不安分
my nipples have been shooting daggers since I woke up.
说真的 自从我父母把我送去军校以来
Seriously, I haven't been this excited
我还没这么激动过
since my parents sent me to military school.
天啊 你出柜以后 一切不该很有趣吗?
God, does everything have to be fun when you're gay?
要是没有 那你就没做对
If it isn't, you're not doing it right.
我只是开心 我到前台来了
I'm just happy I get to be out front here.
我终于不用窝在后厨了(后庭没塞东西)
Finally, I won't be stuffed in the back.
除非我在男厕所撞见
I mean unless I run into a Republican senator
共和党参议员
in the men's room.
快 我们开业吧
Come on, let's open up.
但钥匙在这儿?
But DAT key though?
我太喜欢这份工作了
I love this job.
等等 咱们是不是要来个演讲?
Wait, should someone make a speech?
演讲?
A speech?
如果你想知道我对在机场开店的看法
If you want to hear my thoughts on opening this place,
我可以把我的遗嘱抄送给你
I'll just CC you on my suicide note.
好吧 我来做个演讲吧
Fine, I'll make a speech.
那些说我的口袋太小 永远别想有
To all the school janitors who told me I'd never have
自己的巨型钥匙圈的
my own giant set of keys,
门卫大叔们
too big for any pocket,
和那些说我不是接吻高手的人们
and that I wasn't a good kisser?
统统见鬼去吧
They can all suck it.
耶! 升起来吧 小铁门 升起来吧!
Yes! Rise, gate, rise!
干得漂亮 小铁门
Ooh, you go, gate.
没错 我被权力冲昏了头了
Yes, I'm drunk with power.
不过我确实喝了点小酒
Also, a little drunk.
好了 顾客们都涌进来吧
All right. Here they come.
或许
Yep.
再等等
Any minute.
或许我们点太背了
Just our luck.
赶上今天机场没什么人
The one day the airport isn't crowded.
好吧 我想我可以去男厕
Well, I guess I have time to go check my make-up
补个妆了
in the men's room.
是Han
It's Han.
他想让我们今晚去参加Oleg的告别单身派对
He wants us to come to Oleg's bachelor party tonight.
之前也接到过这种电话
I've gotten a call like this before,
不过通常都是那种贴了流苏胸片
but usually it's through a service that involves
还能两边不同方向甩的舞女打来的
making some tassels spin in opposite directions.
我才不去呢
No way.
你知道的 我打算今晚回家痛哭一场
You know I was planning on going home and crying tonight.
这可是Han策划的派对
Han is planning a party.
肯定能让你哭出来的
You will cry there for sure.
这倒没错 我现在在哪都能哭出来
That's true. I really can cry anywhere now.
我想这点我还是能做到的
I guess I've got that at least.
我简直不敢相信我会在机场工作 Max
I can't believe I work at the airport, Max.
嘿 要是我把钥匙圈给你 你会不会好受点?
Hey, would you feel better if you held my giant keys?
你好?
Hello?
你好
Hello.
欢迎光临 你是我们的第一位顾客
Welcome, you're our first customer.
那有什么奖励吗?
Do I get a prize?
奖品就是你吗?
Is it you?
我上道了 我爱上这份工作了
I'm on board now. I love this job.
大家晚上好
Welcome, everyone.
我是今晚的主持人Han Lee
I'm your M.C., Han Lee,
请允许我以几个风趣幽默的色情笑话
gonna get the crazy party started here
拉开疯狂派对的帷幕
with some dirty, racy jokes.
这是我到过的最死气沉沉的地方
This is the deadest place I've ever been to,
比天堂都死气沉沉
and I once woke up in Heaven.
好 那我们开始吧
Okay, here we go.
魔方和阴茎的共同点是什么?
What do a Rubik's Cube and a penis have in common?
越玩越硬(难)
The more you play with it, the harder it gets.
魔方是上世纪八十年代一种非常流行的玩具
A Rubik's Cube was a popular '80s toy.
弱爆了! 下一个
You suck! Next act.
海象和特百惠(塑料产品品牌)有什么共同点?
What do a walrus and a Tupperware have in common?
等一下
Hold on a minute.
是和密封条有关的...
Something about a seal being tight...
噢!
Oh!
那个飞行员Josh给我发短信了
I just got a text from Josh, the pilot.
他说 "嘿 你在干嘛?"
He says, "What's up, you?"
是不是很可爱?
Isn't that cute?
忘了你的名字很可爱?
Cute that he forgot your name?
你是不是真的很久没恋爱过了?
It's really been a long time for you, hasn't it?
我上周脱了内裤 结果一匹狼嚎叫了起来
I took off my underwear last week and a coyote howled.
太棘手了
Tough crowd.
我是说你 Max
I'm talking about you, Max.
拜托 Han 放轻松
Oh come on, Han. Loosen up.
来 喝一杯
Have a drink.
马提尼 苹果马提尼 随便什么提尼(同"小"的英文发音相同)
A martini, an appletini, anything teeny.
别了 还是来一杯伏特加吧
Nah, just do a vodka shot.
要是没有参照物 伏特加的小酒杯在你手上就和正常酒杯一个大小
If nothing else, the glass will look normal-sized in your hand
我照样能笑
and I'll have a laugh.
伤不了我
Can't hurt.
不过这酒确实挺烈的
But it did.
谢谢你能来帮我主持派对 Han
Thanks for the party, Han.
不过派对什么时候开始啊?
What time is it starting?
我从来没当过伴郎
I've never been a best man.
压力山大啊
It's a lot of pressure.
没错 做一个男人对你来说就挺不容易的
Yeah, being a man would be hard for you.
你还是个小男生呢
You've never been one before.
更别说当伴郎了
Let alone the best one.
这里面都是什么 毛玻璃片吗?
What's in that, ground glass?
呃 这个派对还不如共产党呢
Ugh, this party is worse than the communist party.
共产党可是杀了我一半的家人
And they killed half my family.
Oleg 别担心 我来让大家嗨起来
Oleg, don't worry, I'll get this party started.
我打电话把和我一起上学的妹子叫来
I'm making a call to some girls I went to school with.
我们学校号称是第七街的荡妇学院
The Slut Academy on Seventh.
简称NYU(同纽约大学的简称)
Commonly known as NYU.
我更担心我的堂哥
I'm more concerned about my cousin.
我让他帮我带一些重要的东西
He has something I need.
肥皂? 除臭剂? 还是药效最强的牛皮癣喷雾?
Soap? Deodorant? The toughest actin' Tinactin?
噢 他来了!
Oh, there he is!
嘿 嘿
Hey, hey.
木嘛 木嘛
Mwah, mwah.
好吧 看来不是除臭剂
Well, he didn't bring the deodorant.
Yuri 你赶来了
Yuri, you made it.
你是脱衣舞女吗?
Are you the stripper?
可能几年后就是了
Probably in a few years.
你把文件带来了吗?
Did you bring the papers?
我结婚要用的文件?
The papers I need to get married?
还有我喜欢的乌克兰糖果?
And those little Ukrainian candies I love?
坏消息
Bad news.
那个伪造文件的家伙被驱逐出境了
The guy who made the fake papers got deported.
他们没收了文件
They took the papers.
糖果也被我吃了
I ate the candy.
我错过了什么?
What'd I miss?
除了我成名的机会
Besides my chance to become something?
你是脱衣舞女吗?
Are you the stripper?
不是
Nyet.
褒贬全都涵盖在一个词里了
A compliment and an insult in just one word.
噢 不
Oh, no.
噢 不 不 不
Oh no, no, no, no, no.
我说了"不" 吗?
Did I mention "no"?
你这不是知道"不"的含义吗
How can you say the word "no"
为什么女人说"不"的时候 你却听不懂?
but not understand it when women say it?
简直是晴天霹雳
This is a disaster.
重点是我还没机会浑水摸鱼
And not the kind where I can loot.
我需要这些假文件来给假绿卡续期
I needed those fake papers to renew my fake green card.
我的绿卡下个月就要到期了
Mine expires next month.
什么时候你开始在意保质期了?
Since when do you care about expiration dates?
你煮的那些蛋 老得都能孵出来小鸡跟你打架了
You cook with eggs so old they fight back.
Sophie一定不会相信 我不是为了绿卡
Sophie will never believe that I'm not marrying her
才跟她结婚的
just for a green card.
她很难信任别人
She has major trust issues
因为有一天 她父亲说出去买煎饺...
since one day, her father went out for pierogies and...
可是却空手而归
came back without pierogies.
我还挺喜欢这种展现了
I'm really enjoying the dance stylings
女性下身魅力的舞蹈服装
of Camel and Toe up there.
除了Oleg 大家都很嗨嘛
Everyone is having fun except Oleg.
我还没看见他在这些妹子面前
I haven't seen him so much as put the "V" fingers
举手在嘴边比V的手势
in front of his mouth at any of these ladies.
哦!
Ooh!
我不介意跟这个妞来点出汗的运动
Wouldn't mind some over the sweater action with her.
她的还是你的?
Hers or yours?
Max 我刚做了件我从没做过的事
Max, I just did something I've never done.
讲了个关于别人的故事?
Told a story about someone else?
不 我给那飞行员发了一张裸胸照
No, I sent the pilot a boob pic.
姑娘 你可真下流
Girl, you nasty.
我知道 我好下流!
I know. I am nasty!
我裸着胸看着镜头 就点了发送
I just looked into the camera with my boobs out and hit send.
啊哈 太棒了
Ah-ha, that's awesome.
回到刚才那句
Uh, circling back now,
你说你看着镜头来着?
did you say you looked into the camera?
你没把脸照进去 对吧?
You didn't put your face in it, did you?
姑娘!
Girl!
你可真傻
You stupid.
不这样他怎么知道是我?
How else would he know it was me?
永远不要把脸照进去
You never put your face in it.
我平常都怎么教的你?
Didn't I raise you better than this?
算了 至少你没笑
Well, at least you weren't smiling in it.
好吧 什么样的笑?
All right, what kind of smile?
轻浮的假笑是可以的
A flirty smirk could work.
那种轻佻诱惑的笑更棒
A come-hither grin would be great.
更像是...
More like...
所以你刚刚... 这样
So you were in this... pose
还露着奶子?
with your yabbos out?
也就是说 你刚拍了个裸体酸奶广告
So you basically did a nude yogurt ad.
没错 不过是那种你想上的酸奶 对吧?
Yeah, but like yogurt you want to have sex with, right?
天啊
Oh, my God.
Sophie马上就到了
Sophie will be here any minute.
我打电话时 她在洗头发
When I called, she was washing her hair.
正要把它黏回头上 出门过来
She was going to put it back on her head and come.
跟她讲实话就好
Just be honest with her.
有时候真相是丑陋的
Sometimes the truth is ugly.
她肯定明白 她都看过你裸体了
But she knows that. She's seen you naked.
他还没回短信 肯定不能比这个再丑陋了
Well, still no text back so apparently not as ugly as this.
那是什么意思?
What's that about?
你改做推销房地产的生意了?
Are you selling real estate now?
哇哦
Oh, wow.
这个派对不能更下流俗气了
I mean, this party couldn't get any sleazier
除非你请来罗宾・西克(创作型歌手)
unless you invited Robin Thicke.
这就是一个放荡卖淫城
I'm looking up at skanky whore city,
但我信任你 Oleg
but I trust you, Oleg.
真的?
You do?
真的 为什么不呢?
Yeah, why wouldn't I?
尽管我过去遇到过
Aside from my complicated past
无数个对我撒谎的男人
full of men that have lied to me.
但你我之间没有任何秘密 对吧 Oleg?
But you and I don't have secrets from each other, right, Oleg?
是这样的 听着...
Yeah, well, you see...
现在该伴郎致辞了
It is time for the traditional best man speech.
听好了 婊子们
So listen up, bitches.
该死
Ow, damn it.
我在流血
I am bleeding.
重复 我在流血
Repeat, I am bleeding.
简直不敢相信
I can't believe this.
现在有一摇手机它就能打嗝的软件
There's an app that burps when you shake your phone,
但没有软件能撤回裸胸照?
but no app that unsends a boob pic?
Sophie 还有Oleg
Sophie. Oleg.
关于这两个孩子我能讲点什么呢?
What's there to say about these two kids?
Oleg是个烂厨子
Oleg is a bad cook.
Sophie挺吵闹的
Sophie, quite loud.
但不知为何 他俩在一起时 有奇妙的魅力
But somehow, when they get together, magic.
弱爆了 下一个!
You suck, next act!
在机场工作的小姐如是说
Says the lady that works at the airport.
Oleg 我非常高兴Sophie要嫁给你了
And, Oleg, I'm so glad Sophie is marrying you
这样你就能留在美国了
so now you can stay in the country.
哦 不...
Oh, no. Uh...
弱爆了 下一个?
You suck. Next act?
我懂你 姑娘
Yeah, I hear ya girl.
最后一句话都没有笑点
I mean that last joke didn't even have a punch line.
还有点小悲伤
Yeah, I mean, it was sort of sad.
那不是开玩笑
It was no joke.
是严肃的
This is serious.
这问题真的很严肃
It's really serious.
那张裸胸照已经在云端了
That boob pic is up in the Cloud now.
我的胸在云端了 伙计们
My boob is in the Cloud, y'all.
Sophie 我不知道该怎样告诉你
Sophie, I didn't know how to tell you.
你跟我结婚是为了绿卡?
You wanted to marry me for a green card?
我以为你是因为我的好身材
See, I thought you were marrying me for my bod.
或是因为我在收纳连锁店的人脉 或是...
Or for my connections at The Container Store, or...
我可是教了你识字的!
I mean, I taught you how to read!
Sophie 听我解释
Sophie, I can explain.
不 不 婚礼取消了
No, no, no. The wedding's off.
不
Oh, no.
那群被我涂成新娘白的鸽子
What the hell am I going to do with all those pigeons
该怎么办呢?
that I had painted wedding white?
Sophie 等等
Sophie, wait.
哦 看看这是谁
Aww, well, look who it is.
要被驱逐出境的小亲亲
My dearly deported.
我刚刚一路上都在想这句话
I worked on that the whole way over.
Sophie 我不会被驱逐的
Sophie, I'm not gonna be deported.
我要娶个人 来留在美国
I'm gonna marry someone so I can stay in this country
然后赢回你的心
and win you back.
我不在乎我的新娘是谁
I don't care who my new bride is.
先说好了 不可能是我
Just upfront, it can't be me.
因为所有人都知道我已经嫁给我的事业了
'Cause everybody knows I'm married to my work.
也不能是我
And it can't be me.
就是不能
It just can't.
她们不一定是最好的 甚至不好都行
They don't even have to be the best or even good.
我已经没要求了
Standards are out the window.
看啊 加州葡萄干来了
Look, it's a California Raisin.
墨镜和布洛芬
Ooh. Sunglasses and Advil.
昨晚真是太疯狂了
Last night was mad real.
嘿 Han
Han,
为了我能留在美国 你愿意跟我结婚吗?
will you marry me so I can stay in the country?
我得考虑考虑
I'll need to think about it.
我愿意
Yes.
很明显 他唯一不同意的就只有医保
Apparently the only thing he won't say yes to is health care.
Oleg 我不相信你
Oleg, I don't believe you.
这只是另一个小伎俩 来诱惑我
This is just another trick to get me to do
做你想让我做的事情
what you want me to do.
就像那次你总把冰淇淋"掉"到大腿上一样
Like when you kept "dropping" your ice cream into your lap.
不是伎俩
No trick.
有时 爱会让你做疯狂又恶心的事
Sometimes love makes you do crazy, disgusting things.
像这样
Like this.
过来 Han
Come here, Han.
我现在也爱上这份工作了!
And now I love this job, too!
谢天谢地他选了Han
Thank God he picked Han.
Sophie 听着 Oleg一定很爱你
Wow, Sophie. Oleg must really love you.
那对他来说一定很难
That had to be hard for him.
也能看得出来 Han也有点硬了(难)
And from what I can see, a little hard for Han, too.
咱俩的婚礼上 记得喷两次口气清新剂
At our wedding, maybe two pumps of breath spray.
Han 你不能跟Oleg结婚
Han, you're not marrying Oleg.
因为他要娶的是我
'Cause Oleg's marrying me.
我相信你了
I believe you now.
因为你亲了Han
'Cause you kissed Han,
而你从不喜欢亚洲女生
and Asian girls aren't even your thing.
天啊 Max 是我的裸胸照
Oh my God, Max, it's my boob pic.
有人用它做了个迷因
Someone made it into a meme.
大咪咪迷因?
A mammo meme?
你到四十岁前是不会需要这个的
You're not supposed to need those 'til you're 40.
我的裸胸照片会缠着我一辈子的!
My boob pic is gonna be hanging over me for the rest of my life.
算了吧
Oh, come on,
你的胸连根铅笔都缠不住
your boob couldn't hang over a pencil.